Guide to the Robert B. Fisher Photograph Collection and Papers WA MSS S-2823
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Stereographs, 1850-1975; Series II; 4.2; 5 boxes
  - Ambrotype Stereographs
    - Unidentified photographers
      - Ambrotype stereograph, not in a case, a studio portrait of a man seated, circa 1855-1865 (Box 7, Folder 53)
        Ambrotype stereograph with a black and gilt-painted mount
        Left image broken from top to bottom
  - Tintype Stereographs
    - Unidentified Photographers
      - Tintype stereograph, not in a case, a studio portrait of a man seated, circa 1860 (Box 7, Folder 54)
        Tintype plate crimped on a cardboard mount
      - Tintype stereograph, not in a case, a house with a woman standing in its doorway, circa 1870-1880 (Box 7, Folder 55)
        Hand-tinted tintype unmounted
  - Glass Stereographs
    - Babbitt Tugby
      Babbitt & Tugby was the photographic partnership of Platt Delascus Babbitt and Thomas Tugby in Niagara Falls, New York, 1853-circa 1865
      - American Falls from the Ice Bridge, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Table Rock Horse Shoe Falls -- Canada Side, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Tip Top House, (no number), White Mountain Scenery, (no number), White Mountain Scenery, circa 1860 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Babbitt, Platt Delascus
      Platt Delascus Babbitt was a photographer Niagara Falls, New York, 1847-1873.
      - American Falls from Canada Side, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - The Beauty of Niagara. Rapids rear of Cataract House, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 60)
        Label affixed to recto: "Instantaneous View of Rapids"
      - Cave of the Winds, Niagara, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Ferry Landing, Canada Side, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Grove Scenery in Winter, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 63)
        Partial label affixed to recto: "Bridge across Central Fall encased with.. ."
      - Grove Scenery in Winter; Ferry Grove with group -- American Side, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Horse Shoe Falls from Goat Island, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Horse Shoe Falls, from Ferry, Canada Side, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 66)
        Label affixed to recto duplicates the title on the mount
      - International Hotel, Niagara Falls, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - International Hotel, with Cataract House in the background, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Luna Island Scenery, (No. 157 and no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 69-70)
        Two discrete views of snow on Luna Island, an uninhabited island in Niagara Falls, New York,
      - Niagara Falls from Point View, (No. 29), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Passage under the Great Horseshoe Falls -- Canada Shore, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Point View -- Prince of Wales Suite in foreground, (No. 89), unidentified series, 1860 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Point View, American Side, (no number), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Rope Ascension -- Full view of the Falls from Victoria Point, (No. 81), unidentified series, 1850-1873 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Suspension bridge over Niagara River, (no number), unidentified series, 1855-1873 (Box 8, Folder 76-77)
        Two discrete views of the Niagara Falls Suspension Bridge
      - Suspension Bridge, Niagara, (No. 108), unidentified series, 1855-1873 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Table Rock, Niagara, (No. 153), unidentified series, 1855-1873 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Bierstadt Brothers
      The Bierstadt brothers, Edward Bierstadt (1824-1906), Albert Bierstadt (1830-1902) and Charles Bierstadt (1819-1903), were landscape photographers, painters, illustrators, and engravers. Edward Bierstadt operated the Bierstadt Brothers studio in New Bedford, Massachusetts, circa 1859-1867, and often partnered with his brothers on photographic projects.
      - Boatman at the Pool, Franconia Mountains, N. H., (No. 321), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Fort Lafayette, (No. 656), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Frost Work on Mt. Washington, N. H., (No. 411), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Gibb's Falls, (Third) White Mountain Notch, N. H., (No. 318), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - In Old Fort Putnam, West Point, N. Y., (No. 430), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Mechanics Hall, Boston, Mass., (No. 468), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Old court house in which Daniel Webster sustained his first argument, May 1806, Plymouth, N.H., (No. 210), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Sunny Side: Irving's Residence on the Hudson, N. Y., (No. 577), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 87)
        Home of Washington Irving in Tarrytown, New York
      - Tip Top House, Mount Washington, N. H., (no number), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 88-89)
        Two discrete views of groups at the Tip-Top House, a hotel within the Mount Washington State Park in Sargent's Purchase, New Hampshire
      - View in the Flume, (Winter) Franconia Mountains, N. H., (No. 354), unidentified series, circa 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Chadwick, William Isaac
      William Isaac Chadwick (died 1913) was a British teacher of photography. He also designed stereoscopic cameras.
      - On the Conway River, Betws-y-Coed, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1895 (Box 8, Folder 91)
        Depicts the River Conwy in north Wales.
    - Fenton, Roger
      Roger Fenton (1819-1869) was a pioneer British photographer
      - Panorama pres se la tour Ivan-selik, Moscou, (No. 103), unidentified series, circa 1852 (Box 8, Folder 92)
        View from the Ivan the Great Bell Tower, which includes Cathedral of the Protection of Most Holy Theotokos on the Moat (Saint Basil's Cathedral) and the Spasskaya Tower
      - Raglan Castle, (no number), unidentified series, 1857-1858 (Box 8, Folder 93)
        View of Raglan Castle, north of Raglan, Monmouthshire, Wales
    - Ferrier père, fils Soulier
      Claude-Marie Ferrier (1811-1889) and Charles Soulier (1840-1875) were French photographers. Their partnership operated under the name Ferrier père, fils & Soulier
      - The Old Mill, Wissahickon, Fairmount Park, Philadelphia (U.S.A.), (No. 10214), unidentified series, circa 1864 (Box 8, Folder 94)
      - Vis vue instantanee du pont et de la Place de la Concorde, Paris, (No. 88), unidentified series, circa 1864 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      - Vue générale du glacier du Rhône, (No. 657), unidentified series, circa 1864 (Box 8, Folder 96)
        Inscription in the negative, "Ferrier"
      - Vue générale du Parlement. à Londres, (No. 856), unidentified series, circa 1864 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Ferrier père, fils Soulier, Jules Lévy successeur
      - Echo Lake House, White Mountains, New-Hampshire (U.S.A.), (No. 10233), unidentified series, 1872-1887 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - Rapides de Saint-Anthony. Minnesota. (Amérique.), (No. 10364), unidentified series, 1872-1887 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - The Susquehanna River at Catawissa, Penna. (U.S.A.), (No. 10243), unidentified series, 1872-1887 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Frith, Francis
      Francis Frith (1822-1898) was a British photographer of the Middle East and many towns in the United Kingdom.
      - Portion of the Great Hall of Columns at Karnac, (No. 372), unidentified series, circa 1855 (Box 8, Folder 101)
        Depicts the Karnak Temple Complex in Egypt.
    - Langenheim Brothers
      Langenheim Brothers was a photographic partnership between German American brothers Ernst Wilhelm Langenheim (1807-1874) and Friedrich Langenheim (1809-1879)
      - Catskill Falls, Upper Shute, 180, Lower 80 feet high, (no number), Catskill Mountains, Hudson River, N.Y., circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 102)
      - Doughoregan Manor, Mr. Chas. Carroll's, (no number), Baltimore Vicinity, circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 103)
        From 1766 to 1832, Doughoregan Manor was the country home of Charles Carroll (1737-1832) near Ellicott City, Maryland, last surviving signer of the Declaration of Independence.
      - Fair Mt. Water Works, (no number), Philadelphia series, circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 104)
        Fairmount Water Works on the Schuylkill River, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
      - General view, from the American side, (no number), Niagara Falls, summer view, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 105)
      - Genesee Falls near Portage, New York. Railroad bridge, 230 feet. Upper Falls, 70 feet high, (no number), unidentified series, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      - Genesee Falls, New York. View from the valley from near the sawmill, (no number), unidentified series, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 107)
      - The Mine Hill Gap near Broad Mountain, (no number), Coal Region Near Pittsville, PA, circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 108)
      - Suspension bridge from half mile above the bridge, (no number), Niagara Falls, summer view, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - Terrapin Tower Falls from Goat Island, (no number), Niagara Falls, summer view, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 110)
      - Terrapin Tower from Goat Island, (no number), Niagara Falls, summer view, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - Tuckerman's Ravine, Mount Washington, (no number), White Mountains, New Hampshire, circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - View of the Falls from the whirlpool, (no number), Passaic Falls, Patterson, N. J., circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - Washington's Statue, Union Park, New York, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - Unidentified home and grounds, two men in foreground, (no number), Views of the Most Prominent Country Seats in the Vicinity of New York, circa 1856 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Mason, Samuel J.
      Samuel J. Mason (born 1850) was a photographer and customs officer in Niagara Falls, New York
      - Exterior portrait of a family at Niagara Falls, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 9, Folder 116)
      - Horse Shoe Falls -- Winter, (No. 17), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 9, Folder 117)
      - Suspension Bridge, Interior, (No. 27), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - McPherson, James
      James McPherson (born 1829) was a photographer in Niagara Falls, New York
      - Below Table Rock, (No. 48), unidentified series, circa 1862 (Box 9, Folder 119)
      - Horse Shoe Falls, Winter, (No. 17), unidentified series, circa 1862 (Box 9, Folder 120)
      - Rapids below suspension bridge, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1862 (Box 9, Folder 121)
        Label with an ink inscription affixed to the recto: "This is where Capt. Webb got in to swim." Refers to the death of champion swimmer Captain Matthew Webb (1848–1883) on July 24, 1883, when he jumped from a small boat located near the Niagara Falls Suspension Bridge.
    - Monroe, Myron Hawley
      Myron Hawley Monroe (1824-1912) was a photographer in Rochester, New York, circa 1858 to circa 1883.
      - Trenton Falls, (no numbers), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 9, Folder 122-123)
        Two discrete views of Trenton Falls, Oneida County, New York
    - Stacy, George
      George Stacy (1831-1896) was a photographer in New York State, New Jersey, and South Carolina
      - Soldiers and Guns, Possibly Fort Monroe, Virginia, (no number), Stacy's American Stereoscopic Views, 1861-1865 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Thomson, James
      James Thomson (born circa 1818) was a photographer in Niagara Falls, New York
      - Trenton Falls, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - White, Luther, and Franklin White
      - Equestrian Statue of Jackson, Washington, D.C., (no number), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 9, Folder 126)
      - The Franklin Statue in Court Square, Boston, (no number), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 9, Folder 127)
      - The Gate of the Notch, from the Crawford House, (no number), White Mountain Scenery, circa 1859 (Box 9, Folder 128)
      - Group of horses on the summit of Mt. Washington, (no number), White Mountain Scenery, circa 1859 (Box 9, Folder 129)
      - Tip Top House, Mount Washington, N. H., (no number), unidentified series, 1862 July 27 (Box 9, Folder 130)
        Label with an ink inscription affixed to the verso, which identifies Reuben N. Rice and Charles E. Noble, respectively the General Superintendent and General Agent of the Michigan Central Railroad, as well as their guides
    - Unidentified photographers
      - Eglise St. Pierre, Berlin, (No. 426), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 131)
        Depicts Petrikirche or St. Peter's Church on Petriplatz in Berlin, Germany
      - Engadine Suisse. Panorama de Schuls a sud-ouest, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 132)
        Depicts the town of Scuol in the Graubünden, Switzerland and the Engadine, a valley in the Swiss Alps
      - Exposition Universelle of 1889 at Paris, France, (No. 66), unidentified series (Box 9, Folder 133)
      - Exposition Universelle of 1889 at Paris, France - Interior with display for Villeroy and Boch, (no number), unidentified series (Box 9, Folder 134)
      - Fort and waterfront; men constructing a building in the foreground, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 135)
      - Genre scene, cook kissing a maid, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 136)
      - La gorge de la Sarine a Fribourg (Suisse), (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 137)
        Title from label affixed to the verso. Depicts the Valley of the Saane/Sarine River near Fribourg, Switzerland
      - The Hall. Crystal Palace, London, England, (No. 902), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 138)
      - Niagara Falls, Terrapin Tower Horseshoe Falls from Goat Island, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 139)
        Single image on a glass stereograph plate
      - Panorama de Beaucaire, Midi, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 140)
        Depicts Beaucaire, a commune in the Gard department in Languedoc-Roussillon in southern France.
      - Les piles S. Maurice (Lyon), (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 141)
        Depicts ruins of a Roman aqueduct at St Maurice in Lyon, France
      - Place de la Concorde, Paris, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 142)
      - Place St. Pierre, Rome, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 143)
        The inscription erroneously identifies the images as Saint Peter's Square in Rome, Italy. However, it depicts an ancient Roman equestrian statue of Marcus Aurelius at the Piazza del Campidoglio (Capitoline Hill) in Rome
      - Rome. Place Capitola, (No. 1312), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 144)
        Depicts Piazza del Campidoglio (Capitoline Hill) in Rome
      - Suisse Lucerne Pension Warley et le Mont Pilatus, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 145)
      - Table Rock, Niagara, (No. 153), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 146)
      - Vue de la Compagne du Thoune (Suisse), (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 147)
        View of Thun, Switzerland
      - Vue des Eaux-Bonnes et du Pic de Ger (Pyrénées), (No. 219), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 148)
        View of Eaux-Bonnes and Pic de Ger mountain
      - Vue générale de Mayence, (no number), unidentified series, undated (Box 9, Folder 149)
        General view of Mainz in Rhineland-Palatinate, Germany. Title from label affixed to the verso
  - Salted Paper Print Stereographs
    Salted paper prints are photographic prints whose light-sensitive salts are in the fibers of the paper rather than in a binder; the image is positive and is printed out rather than developed out.
    - American Scenery
      - South Ferry Dock (No. 396), New York City, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Ansiglioni Ottico, Giuliano
      Giuliano Ansiglioni Ottico was an Italian photographer active in Rome, circa 1855-1865
      - Cloaca Massima (No. 69), unidentified series, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 151)
        2nd Underlying Photo: Via del Corso, Roma (No. 150), unidentified series
    - Anthony, Edward
      Arranged sequentially by stereograph number
      Edward Anthony (1819-1888) was an American photographer and a founder of E. & H. T. Anthony & Company
      - The Model of King Solomon's Temple (No. 2), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 152)
      - Broadway (No. 16), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 153)
      - Public Celebration of the Rag Rorums at St. Johnsbury, Vermont, July 4th, 1859 (No. 44), unidentified series, 1859 July 4 (Box 10, Folder 154)
      - Niagara. Table Rock from the Horse Shoe Fall (No. 60), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 155)
      - Niagara. The Horse Shoe Fall from above Table Rock (No. 91), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 156)
      - View in New York Harbor. Steamship Quaker City Coming up the Bay (No. 109), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, 1859 July 4 (Box 10, Folder 157)
      - Niagara. Horse Shoe Fall from near Table Rock (No. 120), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 158)
      - View Near Baltimore. Jones' Falls (No. 183), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 159)
      - View up Broadway, with Stewart's Famous Dry Goods Stores in the foreground (No. 205), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 160)
      - The United States Hotel, New York (No. 210), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 161)
      - The Tomb of Washington (No. 224), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 162)
      - View of the City Hall and Park from Murray Street (No. 233), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 163)
      - New York Bay Scenes: Hauling in the Sheet (No. 237), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 164)
      - Skating Scene in Central Park, New York (No. 259), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 165)
      - Up Broadway from Barnum's Museum, the City Hall Park on the right (No. 301), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 166)
      - Park Row from Tryon Row, the City Hall Park on the right, showing the Times Building and a distant view of St. Paul's Church (No. 309), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 167)
      - Broadway from Barnum's Museum, looking north (No. 321), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 168)
      - The Cascade of St. Anthony, from Below (No. 329), Glimpses of the Great West, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 169)
      - A View of West Point from the Cemetery (No. 367), Beauties of the Hudson, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 170)
      - Locomotive and Train Crossing the Bridge (No. 526), The Picturesque on the Pennsylvania Central R. R., circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - Barnum, Deloss
      Deloss Barnum (1825-1873) was a photographer in New York and Boston, Massachusetts
      - Washington's Headquarters (No. 13), American Historical Series, 1859 (Box 10, Folder 172)
        With a description of the house's history.
      - Suspension Bridge (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 173)
        Includes notation: "C. W. Noyes."
      - Rapids and Whirlpools, Niagara (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 174)
      - Bunker Hill Memorial (no number), unidentified series, 1859 (Box 10, Folder 175)
      - Plymouth Bay (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 176)
      - State House in Boston (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 177)
        Includes notation: "T. T. Oldway."
      - Punch Bowl (No. 94), unidentified series, circa 1855-1865 (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - Beckel Bros.
      The Beckel Bros. was a photographic and optician partnership of Joseph Beckel (1820-1904) and his brother in New York, 1852-1867.
      - View Near Lockport, New York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 179)
      - Niagara Suspension Bridge, American Side (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 180)
      - Mansion on the Hudson River, New York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 181)
      - Trenton Mills, New York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Bierstadt, Charles
      - Full Moon from Negatives taken by Prof. H. Draper, with his Silvered Glass Telescope, (no number), unidentified series, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 183)
      - South Street, looking south, New York (No. 1392), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - C. F.
      - Perspective on a loge in Florence (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 185)
        View of the Loggia dei Lanzi, as well as Fountain of Neptune, in the Piazza della Signoria, Florence, Italy
    - D. Appleton Company
      D. Appleton & Company was an American company founded by Daniel Appleton (1785-1849)
      - The Old Capitol Prison (No. 23), Views of Washington, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 186)
      - The Tomb of Washington, at Mt. Vernon (No. 32), Views of Washington, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - D'Amerval
      D'Amerval was a photographer in Paris
      - L'Amour de Psyché (No. 126), Museé du Louvre, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 188)
        View of the sculpture Psyche Revived by Cupid's Kiss, by Antonio Canova (1757-1822)
    - E. H. T. Anthony Company
      Established by brothers Edward Anthony (1819-1888) and Henry Tiebout Anthony (1814-1884), the E. & H. T. Anthony & Company was the largest supplier and distributor of photographic supplies in the United States during the nineteenth century
      - Broadway (No. 192), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1859 (Box 10, Folder 189)
        With a 2 cent revenue stamp.
      - The Regatta: The winning Boat passing the Judge's Boat (No. 438), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, 1860 July 4 (Box 10, Folder 190)
      - Omnibuses starting from South Ferry, New York (No. 905), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 191)
      - Ferry boat on the East River (No. 908), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 192)
      - Looking down Broadway from the corner of Canal Street (No. 3691), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 193)
      - Broadway, Burst of Sunlight after a Shower (No. 5093), Anthony's Instantaneous Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Edinburgh Stereographic Company
      The Edinburgh Stereographic Company was a firm based in Edinburgh, Scotland, and New York City, which published stereographs, circa 1858-circa 1862
      - Cemetery and Cathedral (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858-circa 1862 (Box 10, Folder 195)
      - House adjoining Cathedral (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858-circa 1862 (Box 10, Folder 196)
      - River and a rocky cliff (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858-circa 1862 (Box 10, Folder 197)
        Inscription on verso: Hawthorn? New?
      - View from Goat Island, Niagara (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858-circa 1862 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Fenton, Roger, attributed